<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Scott Taylor — Personal Site</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Scott Taylor — Personal Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My journey to co-founding entourage</title><link>/posts/my-journey-to-co-founding-entourage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/my-journey-to-co-founding-entourage/</guid><description>&lt;p>Back in 2017, AI was still quite a niche area. It was more focused on deep learning, particularly Recurrent Neural Networks (RNNs) and Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs). If you are part of that cohort, you&amp;rsquo;ll fondly remember OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s website having all of these agents chasing each other in mazes playing various games as they explored reinforcement learning.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the time I was running miDrive, a startup that I had raised ~$10m for, focused on the EdTech sector - bringing learning to drive into the digital age (and all of the transactions that go along with it: first car, insurance, etc.). After much reflection, I had grown the company to a stage that I could feel proud about, and completed much of the innovative product work. And I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but keep being drawn to artificial intelligence at the weekend.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jack Dorsey's bitchat and why tinkering matters</title><link>/posts/jack-dorseys-bitchat-and-why-tinkering-matters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/jack-dorseys-bitchat-and-why-tinkering-matters/</guid><description>&lt;p>I admire people who build things from scratch. Jack Dorsey is one of them. He co-founded Twitter, and although I never agreed with all his decisions there (some moderation choices felt too heavy-handed, too centralised), I like that he keeps experimenting. His latest project, Bitchat, shows why that matters.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Last year, I watched Britain&amp;rsquo;s Online Safety Act pass. It aimed to curb online harm, but it gave the government tools to scan messages and demand backdoors from platforms. I thought, this erodes privacy. We need alternatives. Then Dorsey announced &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://bitchat.free/">Bitchat&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> on X. He built it over a weekend to explore Bluetooth mesh networks. No internet needed.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>On DeepSeek and Export Controls</title><link>/posts/on-deepseek-and-export-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/on-deepseek-and-export-controls/</guid><description>&lt;p>Effective export controls require nuance: preserve open research while mitigating concrete national security risks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We discuss principles for balanced policy design in an increasingly capable AI landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Urgency of Interpretability</title><link>/posts/the-urgency-of-interpretability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/the-urgency-of-interpretability/</guid><description>&lt;p>Interpretability enables us to peer inside complex models and understand the causal pathways behind their outputs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This post outlines practical steps for making interpretability a first‑class priority in safety research.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Anyone else got AI ADHD?</title><link>/posts/ai-adhd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ai-adhd/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me and always have ideas for products, the advent of the AI coding assistant has made it much easier (and quicker) to prove out a hypothesis - alone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Trouble is, my mind never switches off! I now have a long list of trials that I want to experiment with, leading to slight burnout as my brain goes into overdrive.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Want to invent an LLM protocol similar to sitemaps? No problem, just fire up &lt;code>Cursor&lt;/code>. Want to build a health tracking app? No problem, just fire up &lt;code>Cursor&lt;/code>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>You can just build things</title><link>/posts/you-can-just-build-things/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/you-can-just-build-things/</guid><description>&lt;p>There was a meme going around X over the past few days highlighting that if you want to change something, make something, or usher something into existence that &amp;lsquo;you can just build&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And it has never been more true.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>2025 is going to be the year of builders who just jump in with both feet, hack around, inject some creativity, build in public and listen to the feedback loop.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I truly think the non-tech / product manager route has come to an end. And that&amp;rsquo;s speaking as someone who has been &amp;lsquo;product&amp;rsquo; for over a decade. The pivotal fork in the road is for those who ended up becoming more technical (I&amp;rsquo;d count myself in here) and those who didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Typography and Style Demo</title><link>/posts/typography-demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/typography-demo/</guid><description>&lt;p>This page demonstrates the various &lt;strong>typography&lt;/strong> and &lt;em>formatting&lt;/em> options available for content presentation. It serves as both a reference and a testing ground for different styling approaches.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We can emphasize text using &lt;strong>bold formatting&lt;/strong> for strong emphasis, or &lt;em>italic formatting&lt;/em> for subtle emphasis. Sometimes we might need &lt;code>inline code snippets&lt;/code> when discussing technical concepts like &lt;code>useState()&lt;/code> hooks or &lt;code>API endpoints&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For important insights, we can use ==highlight syntax== to draw attention, similar to using a highlighter pen on paper. This ==creates a subtle yellow background== that makes key points stand out without being overwhelming.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>